It's you
who framed my father.
Mr. Qin, you arrived
a bit later than I expected.
Stop playing dumb.
It was you
who caused the crash yesterday.
Breaking news today:
Mr. Qin Shan,
a front-runner in the mayoral election,
unfortunately suffered
a car accident last night
and was severely injured.
After the police intervened,
it turned out that
Qin Shan had taken bribes in the election.
Now Qin Shan is
under police investigation.
The Xinji's Development Project
he was in charge of
has been taken over by his son, Qin Yue.
Now,
do you still want to kill me?
You did all this.
Don't tell me
you expect me to repay you?
Mom, you dressed like that
for hanging out
with your girlfriends again?
What's it to you?
Or do you want to get close to me?
Come along, then.
Good.
I have a lot to say to you, Mom.
[Dearest Episode 7]
Mr. Qin suddenly withdrew from
Xinji's development.
What a pity.
The election is approaching.
I need to fulfill my father's wish first.
and find a new owner for Xinji.
By doing this, I won't let my father down
and can make friends with Mr. He.
Thanks for your trust, Mr. Qin.
To Mr. Qin Shan.
But I'm curious,
why did Mr. Qin
ask to meet me at Cloudsea Club?
Talking business in an entertainment venue
seems absurd, but safe actually.
I've always heard Cloudsea Club
is a place for indulgence,
but seeing it today,
it's truly beyond expectation.
What Mr. He sees here
is just the tip of
the iceberg.
Countless businessmen in this city
come here to unwind.
They shed their masks,
exchange toasts here,
watch the scene,
and scheme in the shadows.
But you should know that
those who can play here
are never truly drunk.
An accident,
an encounter,
can leverage a project worth billions
and determine the layout of a city.
The one who can orchestrate
such a big game
is the real key figure.
The same goes for Xinji's land.
The real owner of it
is Alex, the Boss of Cloudsea Club.
I've long heard of
how resourceful he is.
I've heard of it before.
I heard
he made the connection to
jointly develop Xingji's prime location
with Minister Zhou of the
Resources Bureau.
Outsiders who want in
must work with him.
Mr. Qin, if you'd be willing to help me
get in touch with Mr. Alex,
I'll repay you double when it's done.
Since Mr. He is so sincere,
I'll get straight to the point.
Tonight's meeting
is meant to
bridge the connection
between you and Mr. Alex.
Let's go.
Mr. Alex has been waiting for a long time.
Okay.
Okay. Thank you, Mr. Qin.
Come, please.
Mr. He, this is the Tinghai Suite.
Alex is inside.
Let's go.
Please.
If you like it, I'll give it to you.
It doesn't suit me.
The big one.
Honey, why are you here?
This is Mrs. Wen.
There must be a mistake.
What, you're here to have fun too?
Or
are you going to introduce
the handsome guy next to you?
Mr. He, I'll wait for you outside.
Mr. Qin.
Honey, don't go.
Shouldn't you explain to me
why you are here?
He Mu, you are so dirty.
I'm dirty?
Dirty thing!
Dirty thing! I'll wash you clean!
How can you be laughing?
Xin, I'll protect you!
You slept with my wife
and you dare to hit me?
You dirty thing!
Mr. Qin!
Goodbye. Mr. Qin!
Sir, sir, sir!
Mr. Qin has already gone.
How dare you stop me?
You're just a watchdog!
Dirty thing,
how dare you touch me?
Eat it. Eat it!
You dirty dog, let me clean you up!
Call for help.
Go save him.
Let me wash you clean!
I'll wash you clean!
You dog!
Take your hands off!
Let me go! You dog!
Let me go!
He really hasn't changed,
still so good at
kissing up and kicking down.
Since he loves to bully so much,
let's show him
the consequences.
Step two,
make him stand before
the one he used to bully
and make him feel ashamed.
I must get that land of Xinji.
Grandpa personally promised
that as long as I can get
the development rights for it,
he will let me return to the group.
Whether I can return to
my original position
depends on this time.
He Mu is determined to
get the development rights
to take the position of executive director
and completely control Wenshan Group.
Then I'll let him watch
how this position returns to my hands.
So no matter the cost,
I must win.
We won't let her win, right?
Of course.
Trying to vie with me
won't be that easy.
Chairman He, please have a seat.
The boss will be here shortly.
Mr. Alex, I've heard so much about you.